<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Ramesh > Blog</title><link>https://rvramesh.me/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Ramesh > Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 20:08:38 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rvramesh.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup Active Directory Lab</title><link>https://rvramesh.me/posts/setup-active-directory-lab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 20:08:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rvramesh.me/posts/setup-active-directory-lab/</guid><description>Table of Contents
Install Vagrant
Spin up machines using Vagrant
Machine-A - Active Directory Domain Controller Machine-B - Windows 10 desktop joined to domain Execute the scripts
Results
Machine-A Machine-B Reference
This post will share the details on configuring an Active Directory lab for threat hunting. We will use a popular tool called &amp;ldquo;Vagrant&amp;rdquo; to provision the machines through automation. This post is part-1 of the Auror Project which is hosted by Sudarshan Pisupati</description></item><item><title>Install Nginx Proxy Manager on Raspberry Pi 3B</title><link>https://rvramesh.me/posts/install-nginx-proxy-manager-on-raspberry-pi-3b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 17:49:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rvramesh.me/posts/install-nginx-proxy-manager-on-raspberry-pi-3b/</guid><description>Nginx Proxy Manager acts as a reverse proxy while exposing the services to the network. Using a reverse proxy is good move to improve security and performance.
A reverse proxy is a server that sits in front of your apps and forward client requests to the apps. In other words, we will have to expose one server (Reverse Proxy server) using ports 80 or 443 and we will be able to expose any number of apps that we need.</description></item><item><title>Install Docker and Portainer on Raspberry Pi 3B</title><link>https://rvramesh.me/posts/install-docker-and-portainer-on-raspberry-pi-3b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 16:26:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rvramesh.me/posts/install-docker-and-portainer-on-raspberry-pi-3b/</guid><description>Table of Contents
About Docker and Portainer Instructions to install Docker and Portainer Docker installation Portainer installation Reference About Docker and Portainer Docker might be a familar term. If this term is new to you, then Docker is a container management service. Dockers are pretty lightweight and have the ability to reduce the size of an application through a smaller footprint of the operating system and the application infrastructure.
Docker containers can be deployed anywhere, on any physical machines,virtual machines or also on the cloud.</description></item></channel></rss>